Hello, my name is Rika Nakayama, Siri TV lead, seat number 12.
I am very happy to announce that my music video with Earphone Lion has been viewed 1.2 million times,
I'm happy to finally share my personal video with you.
Yay! Thank you all so much.
What I will be doing this time is a one-day interview during idol porn.
I'm going to do a one-day live performance.
I really like to watch idols and YouTubers' one-day live performances,
I have a very detailed schedule in AV.
I will share it with you.
I hope you enjoy it.
Loud applause
Thank you very much.
Big applause
Applause
Big clap
Ooh
Ooh!
Oh, I'm done.
We've been filming all day, so how many times can you do a lot of things?
Yes, sir.
The stage, oh, what was that? We're done.
I'm going to start the second part later.
Too soon.
This is today's stage.
I did it earlier.
I'm off to do hair and makeup.
I'm laughing, I'm laughing now
I'm for life
A present from us.
Please take care and accept it!
Hello.
Here
Eat a lot
Keep your stamina up.Build up your stamina.
What are you taking? Tomatoes?
I want tomatoes.
I'm going to eat after rehearsal.
What shall we eat?
White rice, definitely.
But don't eat anything oily.
This time...
Last time, I want you to hear this...
They served crab cream croquettes.
Who had it?
Then again, it's a bit of a show.
You know, it smells like a potato.
It smells bad.
That's why I really don't like fried food before the show.
Bottom line.
I have a music video with Earphones Lion from two years ago.
1.2 million views, and I'm making a personal video.
I'll take a picture of that when I change out of my costume.
I'll make sure I don't forget that.
I'm going to go have dinner and get my hair and makeup done.
Who's that?
I can't seem to fix my makeup.
How am I supposed to fix it?
It's annoying.
Look, there's a little...
It's hard to fix my makeup.
This is my favorite kind of lamé. Only in reverse.
Hey, here it is.
What flavor of single lamé shadow? Melinda Melinda Beige.
It's in. It's in. It's beautiful.
Wait a minute. I hope you don't have fish stuck in your teeth.
How do you spend your time before the show?
The doctor's not here today.
Not everything has an attitude.Not everything has an attitude.
There are going to be moments where we're going to have to do it ourselves.
You're going to see a little bit of my feet open a little bit sober.
My partner, the bamboo stomp. Bamboo stomp? What's this? Bamboo.
Every time I step on it, I'm protecting it in the countryside.
Where is it? There's no white wall.
Put it down first. It's easy.
Take off your shoes. Kumamoto is here.
Take off your shoes. You can see Kumamoto.
It feels good.
Live mileage... 5 more minutes.
I'll be dressed in five minutes.
Please lift the bamboo.
Where did you get it?
Where's the Internet? I bought them online.
For stepping on?
For stepping on.
Bamboo, green bamboo.
Mmm-hmm.
It really helps the sole of your foot.
This song is the most popular album in Japan.
I've been putting people on my back
Oh, now I'm riding on this rhythm
I've conveyed the words in my heart
Kanazawa Fashion
Sweet Allergy
SweetSweetie.
# You love me
♪ You'll see me tomorrow ♪
Samphreference! Samphreference! Samphreference!
Let's all hold hands.
Now that the concert is over
I've been spending some time
I just took a bath.
I feel refreshed.
I'm moisturizing my face now.
After this
I'm going back to the hotel.
We're done.